A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991, RG 39 FA1505
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991; 39
  - Commercial Venture, 1987-1991; 8
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - A-B (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - C-M (Box 97, Folder 1-4)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - Global Investment Forum (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - International Advisory Committee (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - N-Z (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Insurance - A-Z (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Conservation, 1987-1991; 9
    - Conservation - A-B (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Conservation - C-J (Box 99, Folder 1-4)
    - Conservation - K-R (Box 100, Folder 1-4)
    - Conservation - S-Z (Box 103, Folder 1-3)
    - Conservation - A-E - Cousins (Box 101, Folder 3-5)
    - Conservation - F-Z - Cousins (Box 102, Folder 1-9)
    - Campfire Conservation Fund - A-Z (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Clean Water Fund (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Commonweal (Research Institute) (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - The Conservation Foundation (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Conservation Law Foundation of New England (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Conservation Law Foundation of New England - Cousins (Box 104, Folder 2-3, Box 105, Folder 1)
    - The Coolidge Center for Environmental Leadership (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - The Coolidge Center for Environmental Leadership - Cousins (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Defenders of Wildlife (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Defenders of Wildlife - Cousins (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Rene Dubos Center for Human Environments, Inc. (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Environmental Action Foundation (Box 105, Folder 4, Box 107, Folder 1-2)
    - Environmental Defense Fund (Box 106, Folder 6, Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Environmental Defense Fund - Cousins (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Environmental and Energy Study Institute (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Environmental Policy Institute (Box 108, Folder 1-3, Box 109, Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Green Century Project - Cousins (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Friends of the Earth Foundation (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - The Green Century Project (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - League of Conservation Voters (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - National Audubon Society (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - National Audubon Society - Contributions (Box 111, Folder 4-5)
    - National Audubon Society - Contributions - Cousins (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - National Celebration of the Outdoors (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - National Toxic Hazards Prevention Fund (Box 112, Folder 2-3, Box 113, Folder 1)
    - National Wildlife Federation (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - National Wildlife Federation - Cousins (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council (Box 114, Folder 3-4, Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Contributions (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Contributions - Cousins (Box 113, Folder 3, Box 117, Folder 1-2)
    - Nature Conservancy (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Nature Conservancy - Cousins (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - New York Zoological Society (Box 115, Folder 4, Box 116, Folder 1)
    - New York Zoological Society - Board of Trustees (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - New York Zoological Society - The Bronx Zoo (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - New York Zoological Society - Central Park Zoo (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - New York Zoological Society - Contributions (Box 116, Folder 5, Box 118, Folder 1)
    - New York Zoological Society - Contributions - Cousins (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - New York Zoological Society - Fundraising (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - New York Zoological Society - Meetings (Box 118, Folder 3, Box 119, Folder 1)
    - New York Zoological Society - Printed Matter (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Northern Plains Project (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Rails to Trails Conservancy (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Renew America (Box 120, Folder 2-3)
    - Restoring the Earth (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Save-The Redwoods League (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Shelburne Farms (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Shelburne Farms - Cousins (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Scientists' Institute for Public Information (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Southwest Research and Information Center (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Student Conservation Association, Inc. (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - United States Government (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - A-Z (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Park Foundation - A-Z (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - Parks - A-Z (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - 75th Anniversary (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - Parks - Acadia National Park (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - Parks - Grand Teton National Park (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - Parks - A - Cousins (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - United States Government - President's Commission on Americans Outdoors (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - World Resources Institute (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - World Resources Institute - Cousins (Box 124, Folder 1-2, Box 125)
    - Miscellaneous States - A-Z - Cousins (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous States - Maine - A-Z - Cousins (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous States - Maine - Maine Coast Heritage Trust (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous States - Maine - Maine Coast Heritage Trust - Cousins (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous States - Maine - Natural Resources Council of Maine (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous States - Maine - Natural Resources Council of Maine - Cousins (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous States - A-Z (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous States - Maine A-Z (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous States - Massachusetts - A-Z - Cousins (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - New York State - A-Z (Box 127, Folder 1-3)
    - New York State - K-R - Cousins (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - New York State - The Adirondack Council (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - New York State - The Adirondack Council - Cousins (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - New York State - Benmarl Vineyards (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - New York State - Hudson River Foundation (Box 128, Folder 2-3)
    - New York State - Hudson River Valley Association (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - New York State - Hudson River Valley Greenway Council (Box 130, Folder 2-3)
    - New York State - Hudson Riverkeeper Fund, Inc. - Cousins (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - New York City - A-Z - Cousins (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - New York State - Scenic Hudson - Cousins (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - New York City - A-Z (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - New York City - Central Park Conservancy (Box 131, Folder 1-4)
    - New York City - Central Park Conservancy - Cousins (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - New York City - Central Park Conservancy - A-Z (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - New York City - Central Park Conservancy - Board of Trustees (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - New York City - Central Park Conservancy - Contributions (Box 132, Folder 4-5)
    - New York City - Central Park Conservancy - Finances (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - New York City - Central Park Conservancy - Fundraising - General (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - New York City - Central Park Conservancy - Fundraising - A-Z (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - New York City - Central Park Conservancy - Meetings (Box 134, Folder 1-2, Box 135, Folder 1)
    - New York City - Central Park Conservancy - Printed Material (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - New York City - A-Z (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - New York City - Council on the Environment of New York (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - New York City - Department of Environmental Protection (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - New York City - New York City Street Consortium (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - New York State - New York Parks and Conservation Association (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - New York State - New York Parks and Conservation Association - Nash Castro Speech Reprint (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - New York State (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - New York State - Environmental Bond Issue, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - New York State - Palisades Interstate Park Commission (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - New York State - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Annual Reports (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - New York State - Rockefeller State Park Preserve (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - New York State - Scenic Hudson, Inc. (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - New York State - Tappan Zee Preservation Coalition (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous States - Texas - A-Z (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous States - Texas - National Wildflower Research Center (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous States - Texas - National Wildflower Research Center - Meetings (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous States - Texas - National Wildflower Research Center - Contributions (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous States - Texas - National Wildflower Research Center - Cousins (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous States - Vermont - River Watch Network (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous States - Vermont - A-Z (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous States - Vermont - A-Z - Cousins (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous States - Wyoming - A-Z (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Parks - A-Z (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Parks - A-Z - Cousins (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Parks - The Parks Council (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Foreign - A-Z (Box 140, Folder 1-3)
    - Foreign - A-Z - Cousins (Box 145, Folder 2-4)
    - Foreign - Brazilian Association for the Preservation of Wildlife (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Foreign - Conservation International (Box 141, Folder 1-3)
    - Foreign - Conservation International - Cousins (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Foreign - International Wilderness Leadership Foundation (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Foreign - International Wilderness Leadership Foundation - Cousins (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Foreign - World Wildlife Fund (Box 142, Folder 2-3)
    - Foreign - World Wildlife Fund - Cousins (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Recreation - A-I (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Recreation - J-Z (Box 143, Folder 1-2)
    - Recreation - A-Z - Cousins (Box 145, Folder 8-9)
    - Recreation - National Fitness Foundation (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Recreation - New York Junior Tennis League (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - D-E, 1987-1991; 10
    - D - Miscellaneous (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Defense - A-Z (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Defense - A-Z - Cousins (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Defense - Veterans (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Defense - Veterans - A-Z - Cousins (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Defense - Desert Storm Homecoming Foundation (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Defense - Navy League of the United States (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - E - Miscellaneous (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Economics, 1987-1991; 11
    - Economics - A-B (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Economics - C-H (Box 146, Folder 1-3)
    - Economics - I-T (Box 147, Folder 1-3)
    - Economics - U-Z (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Economics - C-I - Cousins (Box 145, Folder 12-15)
    - Economics - J-Z - Cousins (Box 149, Folder 1-3)
    - American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Bretton Woods Committee (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Caribbean Basin Initiative (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Business Professional People for the Public Interest (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities (Box 149, Folder 5, Box 150, Folder 1-3)
    - Center for Resource Economics (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Council on Economic Priorities (Box 151, Folder 1-3, Box 152, Folder 1)
    - The Development Training Center (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Edwards, Ronald Delano (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Employment Research Associates (Box 152, Folder 3-4)
    - Foundation on Economic Trends (Box 154, Folder 1-2)
    - Institute for International Economics, 1987-1991 (Box 153, Folder 2-3)
    - Institute for International Economics - The Blackstone Group (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Institute for International Economics - Meetings (Box 153, Folder 5, Box 155, Folder 1-2)
    - Institute for International Economics - Printed Material (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - International Academy of Management (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Manhattan Institute for Policy Research (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Manhattan Institute for Policy Research - Cousins (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Northeast Midwest Institute (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Northeast Midwest Institute - Cousins (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Rebuild America (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - The Rockford Institute (Box 157, Folder 1-2)
    - Taxes-Taxation (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Trilateral Commission - A-Z (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Trilateral Commission - Fundraising, 1988 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Trilateral Commission - Fundraising, 1991 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Trilateral Commission - Meetings, 1987-1991 (Box 158, Folder 3-4)
    - Trilateral Commission - Contributions (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Trilateral Commission - Meetings, 1989-1991 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Trilateral Commission - Printed Matter (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - US-USSR Trade and Economic Council, Inc. (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Education, 1987-1991; 12
    - Education - A-B (Box 159, Folder 4-5)
    - Education - C-H (Box 160, Folder 1-4)
    - Education - I-P (Box 161, Folder 1-4)
    - Education - Q-Z (Box 162, Folder 1-3)
    - Education - A-H - Cousins (Box 156, Folder 3-8)
    - Education - I-V - Cousins (Box 163, Folder 1-5)
    - Education - W-Z - Cousins (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - A Better Chance (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - A Better Chance - Cousins (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - American Academy of Achievement (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - American Philosophical Society (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Aspen Institute (Box 165, Folder 3, Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Center for American Studies at Concord (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Earthwatch (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Earthwatch - Cousins (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Esalen Institute (Box 166, Folder 3-4, Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Esalen Institute - Cousins (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Esalen Institute - Revisioning Philosophy Program (Box 167, Folder 2-3)
    - Esalen Institute - Soviet American Exchange Program (Box 168, Folder 1-2)
    - Esalen Institute - Soviet-American Exchange Program - Cousins (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Foundation for American Communications (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Global Education Associates (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Global Education Associates - Cousins (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Global Studies Center (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Committee on Scholastic Achievement (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - The Hastings Center (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - The Hastings Center - Cousins (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Institute of International Education (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Institute for Media Analysis, Inc. - Cousins (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Institute for Policy Studies - Cousins (Box 170, Folder 1-2)
    - Institute for 21 Century Studies (Box 171, Folder 5-6)
    - International Center for Integrative Studies, Inc. (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - International Center for Integrative Studies, Inc. - Cousins (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Leaders in the New Civilization (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Leaders in the New Civilization - Cousins (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Life Actions (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Lindisfarne Association, Inc. (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Meadowcreek Project (Box 173, Folder 1-2)
    - National Geographic Society (Box 173, Folder 3-4)
    - National Geographic Society - A-Z (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - National Geographic Society - Board of Trustees (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - National Geographic Society - Finances (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - National Geographic Society - Fundraising (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - National Geographic Society - Minutes/Meetings (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - National Humanities Center (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - New Dimensions Foundation (Box 174, Folder 6, Box 175, Folder 1)
    - New Dimensions Foundation - Cousins (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Ojai Foundation (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Ojai Foundation - Cousins (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Recruiting Young Teachers, Inc. (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Recruiting Young Teachers, Inc. - Cousins (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - S.A.I.L., Inc. (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - San Francisco Education Fund (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Saybrook Institute (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Saybrook Institute - Cousins (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Snake River Institute (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Public Interest Research Group of Education Fund (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - US-USSR Youth Exchange Program (Box 177, Folder 2-3)
    - Wainwright House (Box 176, Folder 3-4, Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Wainwright House - Cousins (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - A (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - B-G (Box 179, Folder 1-3)
    - Colleges - H-Me (Box 182, Folder 1-5)
    - Colleges - Mi-O (Box 183, Folder 1-4)
    - Colleges - P-S (Box 184, Folder 1-3)
    - Colleges - T-Z (Box 185, Folder 1-3)
    - Colleges - A-Mo - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 180, Folder 1-10)
    - Colleges - N-Z - Cousins (Box 181, Folder 1-7)
    - Colleges - American College of Orgonomy (Box 185, Folder 4, Box 186, Folder 1-2)
    - Colleges - American University of Beirut (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Bard College (Box 186, Folder 4, Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Bard College - Cousins (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Bard College - Institute of Health Policy and Practice (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Barnard College (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Barnard College - Cousins (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Beirut University College (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Bentley College (Box 188, Frame 1)
    - Colleges - Boston College (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Boston College - Cousins (Box 189, Folder 3-4)
    - Colleges - Boston University (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Boston University - Cousins (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Brown University (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Brown University - Center for Foreign Policy Development - Cousins (Box 189, Folder 7, Box 190, Folder 1-3, Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Brown University - Cousins (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - California Institute of Integral Studies (Box 188, Folder 5, Box 191, Folder 1-2)
    - Colleges - California Institute of Integral Studies - Cousins (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Cambridge College, Cambridge, MA (Box 191, Folder 3, Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Cambridge College, Cambridge, MA - Cousins (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Carthage Institute of Technology (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Center for Theology and Natural Sciences (Box 192, Folder 3-4)
    - Colleges - City University of New York - A-Z (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - City University of New York - A-Z - Cousins (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - City University of New York - Graduate School University Center (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - City University of New York - Graduate School University Center - Cousins (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - City University of New York - Fiorello H. Laguardia Community College (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - City University of New York - Fiorello H. Laguardia Community College - Cousins (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - City University of New York - Queens College (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - City University of New York - Queens College - Cousins (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - Colleges - City University of New York - Queens College - Center for the Biology of Natural Systems (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - College of the Atlantic (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - College of the Atlantic - Cousins (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - Colleges - Columbia University (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - Cousins (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - A-Z (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - American Assembly (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - American Assembly - Cousins (Box 195, Folder 2-3)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - School of International and Public Affairs (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - Conference on Science and Religion (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - Oral History Research Project and Office (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Cooper Union (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - Cornell University - A-Z (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - Colleges - Cornell University - A-Z - Cousins (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Cornell University - Center for Religion, Ethnics and Social Policy (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Dartmouth College - A-Z (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Dartmouth College - A-Z - Cousins (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Curtin University of Technology, Perth, Western, Australia (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Dartmouth College - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for Social Sciences (Box 197, Folder 3-4)
    - Colleges - Dartmouth College - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for Social Sciences - Cousins (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Duke University (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Duke University - Cousins (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Emory University (Box 197, Folder 5, Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Emory University - Cousins (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - Earlham College (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Georgetown University (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Gettysburg College (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Printed Material (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Hampshire College (Box 201, Folder 7, Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - A-Z (Box 200, Folder 1-3)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - H-Z - Cousins (Box 202, Folder 2-3)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Contributions - A-Z (Box 204, Folder 1-4)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Contributions - A-Z - Cousins (Box 202, Folder 5-7)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Center for International Affairs (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Center for International Affairs - Cousins (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Divinity School (Box 200, Folder 4, Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Divinity School - Cousins (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - John King Fairbank Center for East Asian Research (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard College Fund (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard College Fund - Cousins (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Graduate Society (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Medical School (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Medical School - Cousins (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Medical School - Center for Psychology Studies (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Medical School - Center for Psychology Studies - Cousins (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Medical School - A-Z (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - John F. Kennedy School of Government (Box 206, Folder 1-3)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - John F. Kennedy School of Government - Cousins (Box 203, Folder 6)